Best Health Insurance Plans 2026:
In this video, we have brought for you the top plans of 2026.  In this
we will talk about what are the plans?
What is their claim ratio?  What are the benefits
?  What is the eligibility criteria?  Finally,
we will also compare the premiums
for you.  But one disclaimer, please do your due diligence.
We have compared these plans on different parameters.  But you should do
your due diligence.  See
which plan is more beneficial for you.  Please
proceed accordingly.
Quick reminder before starting the video,
if you have not yet subscribed to our channel then do it so that
you get the right
information at the right time let's move
towards the video Most awaited video of the year Best
Health Insurance Plans 2026 Here we
will compare six plans, which are
Neevapar Rush 3.0 HDFC Ergo Optima
Secure ICICI Lombard Elevate Base Plan
Aitya Birla Activ Max Manipal Cigna
Sarvaha Param & Care Supreme Plan So
first let's talk about the Incred Claim Ratio,
what is the Incred Claim Ratio of these companies
?  The income claim ratio has been taken as per the latest IADA annual report as on 31st March 2025.
Nivapa's
income claim ratio is 61.22%
HDFC Aego Optima Secure is 84.85% ICICI
Elevate is 82.34%
Aitya Bl Activ Max is 71.5% Manipal Sigma
is 74.81%
and Care Supreme Plan is 64.53%
Now let's talk about what is the USP of these plans
?  What are the unique selling points
of these plans?  Neeva Reader 3 Point
comes with the option of unlimited sum assured.  There
is no sum assured.  There
is unlimited coverage.  You can claim as much as you want.  There
are 145 pre-existing diseases
which you can cover from day one by paying extra premium.  The
unique selling point of HDFCR Optima Secure is that
your 2x 3x cover counts from day one.
Meaning, if you have taken Optima Secure one
year, two year or three year policy then
you will get cover two times.  If the policy is for Rs 10
then it is Rs 20, if it is Rs 20 then it is Rs 40, if it is Rs 40 then it is Rs 80 and
if you pay the premium of 3 years together in
Super Secure then you get 3x count there.
Three times count from
day one.  This is the USP of HDSC Ego
Optima Secure Plan.  There are many riders
available.  Like parenthood, you
can get maternity cover.  If you want
Day One cover of Asthma, BP,
Cholesterol, Diabetes, you can take that also.   If you
want infinite cover, that rider
is also available.  There are many more options
including OPD rider also.
Their USP in ICICI Lombard Elevate is the Power
Booster.  This means that your sum insured will keep
increasing by 100% every year.  There is no
upper limit also.  There is an inbuilt civil
discount that if your CIBIL score
is good, you get civil discount
up to 20%.  Infinite Care Rider
is available where you
can claim an infinite amount.  If you have opted
for this rider.  Then there is a rider called
Jump Start.  Where you can get day one cover.
Day one coverage of asthma, BP, cholesterol, diabetes etc.  Aditya
Birla Activ Max offers you an enhanced sum assured of up to 500%.
Your
cumulative bonus keeps increasing every year and can
increase up to 500%.  There
is also chronic care where you can get asthma, BP,
cholesterol, diabetes, obesity etc.
covered from day one.  Another
higher variant of this is Vital Plan where
policy is available for some conditions like stunting, COPD etc.
So you can refer that also.
Detailed videos of all these plans
are also available on our channel.  We will be brief here
because we are doing a comparison.
Manipal Singhana Sarawaha is the biggest USP in the Param plan.
There is no waiting period.
This is a plan with zero waiting period.
You do not have an initial waiting period, a
slow-growing illness waiting period, or a
waiting period for pre-existing diseases.  So, there are
no waiting periods here.  But if you want to
add waiting periods, you can do so.
Your premium gets reduced.  Meaning
you are already instant in it, meaning there is
no waiting period.  But you are putting await.
Meaning, if you are adding weight then
your premium will reduce.
Talking about Care Supreme, there is an option of instant cover here.  There
is an option of Super NCB which
makes this plan attractive.  Let's talk about
eligibility.  The first thing we talk about
whenever we compare any plans is
room rent,
what is the room rent eligibility?  Neema Reshore
3.0 comes in four variants:
Classic, Select, Elite and Black.  So
Classic and Select have general ward and
twin sharing room respectfully.  The Elite
plan offers a single private AC room.  And
if you don't want any category restrictions
then go for the Black plan.
No room rent capping in HDFC Optima Secure
You can use any room as per
actuals.  ICIC Elevate also has single
private AC rooms but room modifier
option is available through which you can upgrade
or downgrade your room i.e. get a room on twin sharing basis.
Or you
can remove the room restriction for a single room.   There is
no room run capping at Aditya Birla Active & Max either.
You can downgrade by taking room modification.  Manipal
Signal Sarva has single private AC room.  There is
no room rent capping in the Care Supreme plan.  You can opt for any room.
Minimum and maximum entry age.  So
what is the minimum age to enter the policy?
For an adult.  The minimum entry age is 18
years in all the policies.  There is
no maximum entry age in A reshore 3.0.  Even if you
are 80 years old, you can take the policy.
HDFC Optima Secure does
not have a maximum age limit.  You
can enter this policy at any age.  ICIC LBA
is 125 years old in Elevat.  So essentially there
is no maximum entry age.  There is no
limit on Aditya Virla Activ and Max also.  There is
no limit in Manipal Sidna and there is no limit in Care Supreme also.
So, earlier IDA guidelines
came where they said that everyone should
get insurance.  So there
should not be a maximum entry age limit.  So
all these policies are designed in such a way that there is
no maximum entry age limit.  You
can enter this policy at any time.  Now,
if a family floater policy is taken, then there are
dependents also.  There are children in it.
So his age starts from 91 days.
After three months they can be added to the policy.
And the maximum it goes up to is
30 years in Neema Bhupa.  In HDFC and Optima
Secure, dependents can remain added for up to 25 years.
ICC Low LBA Elevate has 30
Years.  Aditya Birla Active One Max can
last up to 25 years.  Dependent
Child can be added up to 91 years in Manipal Sinha Sarvaah Plan and up to
30 years in Care Supreme Plan.
Minimum and Maximum Sum Insured
How much sum insured policy can you take
?  As we discussed in Divor 3.0, there
is an option of unlimited sum insured.  You can avail sum insured ranging
from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 2 crore in HDFC Aego Optima Secure.
ICICI LB Daily offers the
option of sum insured ranging from Rs 5 lakh to unlimited.  Aitya Birla
Activ has an option of Rs 7 lakh to Rs 6 crore.
ManipalCigna Saravaha plan has options ranging from Rs 5 lakh to Rs
3 crore.  And Care
Supreme has a sum insured option ranging from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 1 crore.
You can choose any sum
insured as per your need.  We will
talk about the policy tenure, for
how many years you can take the policy.
Neevapa 3.0 can be taken simultaneously for up to 1 2 3 4 5 years.
Meaning what is
called multi tenure policy.  If you
take multitenure, there are two benefits.
Firstly, you get a discount.  You are
paying the premium together.  Secondly, if
your premium increases in the future due to inflation, then
that impact will
not be on your policy.  If you have taken a multi-tenure
policy, then you can take a 5-year policy together with Niva 3.0.
HDFC Optima
Secure One Year Two Year Three Year Options
Available.  ICICI Ltd Elevate
is also available with tenure options ranging from one to five years.   You
can take Aditya Birla Active and Max One Year Two Year Three Year, Manipal Cigna Sarvaha One Two Three Years and Care Supreme also One Two Three Years policy.  Let's
talk about bonuses.  The bonus is a cumulative
bonus.  No Claim Bonus Loyalty Bonus.  You can
understand anything.  You don't take a claim.  If you
are loyal to the company then the company gives you some
bonus on renewal.  So there
is no concept of bonus in NIMA 3.0 because here there
is unlimited sum insured, so there will be
no bonus because there is no sum insured.   There
is no limit.  You
can claim as much as you want.  Then comes HDFC
Ergo Optima Secure.  Here you
get pay plus benefit which is 50% every year
maximum goes to 100%.  Meaning, if you have
taken a policy of 10 lakhs, next year it will become 15 lakhs
and above that it will become 20 lakhs.  So
your ad increases by 50-50% and becomes 1X in the next two
years.  This is Loyalty Edition.  This has nothing to do with the claim.
You get a 20% cumulative bonus in ICIC LBAD Elevate.
The maximum goes up to 100% every year.
Policy of Rs 10 lakh for next year 12, 14, 16, 18 and
20.  On top of that, you can avail Power Booster
to increase your sum assured by 100% every year.  Then comes Aditya Birla Activ Max
100% your growth every year.
This goes up to a maximum of 500%.  Manipal Singh Sarwaha will talk about Param.  There is a piggy
bank here which increases your sum
assured.  Guaranteed
increase of 100% every year maximum up to
1000% i.e. your sum insured increases up to 10 times in
these 10 years.  Care
Supreme is 50% Maximum 100%.
You can take Super NCB on top of this.  Super No Claim
Bonus which takes the sum insured to X.
Day care hospitalization
is covered in all policies up to the sum insured.   Then
comes domiciliary hospitalization.
Domiciliary hospitalization
is also covered in all policies up to Sum Assured Domiciliary
where you are taking treatment at home.
It is also called hospital at home.  Meaning this happens in two conditions
where beds are not available in the hospital.  The
patient is so critical that he
cannot be taken to the hospital.  So domiciliary
hospitalization will be covered as per policy
terms and conditions up to sum insured.
Giving Ayush Hospitalization.  AYUSH means
Ayurveda, Yoga, Unani, Siddha,
Homeopathy.  They also undergo hospitalization.
So their hospitalization
is also covered in your policy.  Ah, that means AYUSH has its
own hospitals.  So if
hospitalization is happening, it
is medically necessary, then Ayush hospitalization
is also covered up to the sum insured.  Now let's talk about
refill benefit, restore
benefit.  This is the benefit where
your sum insured is exhausted.
Suppose you use the entire sum insured in a year,
then what after that?  So
after that the company refills your sum insured.
So it's called the Refill Restore Benefit.
So refill benefit
is not available in Neevapa Reshore 3.0 as it is an unlimited
sum insured policy.  So there
is no concept of refill in Niva 3.0.  Because there
is no sum insured.  You
can claim as much as you want.
Once a year refill is available at HDFC Ergo Secure.  For same
person, same illness, different person, different
illness.  There are no restrictions.
You can convert this into unlimited restore benefit
by paying a nominal additional premium.
Unlimited number of times refill is available in ICICI Lo LBAD Elevate
for any
illness.  There is no restriction.  Then comes
Aditya Birla Activ Max,
unlimited is also available in this.  And
unlimited refill is also available in Manipal Cigna Sarvaha
and unlimited refill is also available in Care Supreme
for any illness.  Emergency Road
Ambulance.  So the road ambulance that we use
to go to the hospital.  So what
expenses are covered for that?  Nima Reshore 3.0 has
Actual on Edge.  We will pay whatever the actual expenses are.
HDFCO Optima Secure
also has S per actual.  ICIC LBA
is also available in Elevate.  Manipal Cigna
also has actual stake in Aditya Birla.  Manipal
is also active in Cigna.  In Care Supreme,
if the sum insured is less than Rs 15 lakh, then it is
Rs 10,000.  If the amount is above Rs 15 lakh then
actual pay will be made.  Emergency Air
Ambulance.  The Niva Recharge 3.0 offers
emergency air ambulance cover up to 5 lakh.  But
hospitalization.  HDFC Ago has 5 lays.
You can also add as a rider in ICIC LBD
for emergency air ambulance.  And you can
also add As a Rider to Aditya Birla Active One.
Manipal Sinh Saravaha Param also has an
add on rider with a maximum of 10 layaways and Care
Supreme plan gives you up to 5 layaways.  This
is also an optional rider.  And the
5 LE I'm talking about in the Nivapa 3.0 is in your Alt and
Black variants and
not the Classic selection.  Now let's talk about
annual health checkup.  Annual health checkup
is optional in NIBA 3.0.  If you want to
get preventive health checkup annually, then
you can add this rider by paying
additional premium.  HDFCO Optima Secure
is inbuilt.  You can claim this on renewal
up to ₹15,000. LBR
also has a rider as an option which you
can add and claim on cashless basis
from the first year itself.
Your Aitya is also available in Bla Activ Max.
Preventive health checkup
is complimentary once a year.  Once a Year is
also complimentary in ManipalCigna Sir Plan
and is also included in Care Supreme.
Once a year complimentary.
Wellness benefits.  Wellness benefits are basically
those that give you additional benefits.
Meaning, illness is covered in your policy as
we understand.  Butt wellness is also a
focus.  We also focus on your health.
Neeva 3.0 has Live Healthy
benefit where you walk a certain number of
steps daily on the basis of which
you get up to 30% discount
on renewal or you have to download their app
and keep tracking it.
No such benefit is available in HDFC ARGO.  Your wellness benefit is also available in your ICICI LBAD.
Where
you are given a discount of up to 20%.
Aditya Birla Activ Max
offers health returns up to 100%.  Yes,
up to 100% and actual people have got it too.
Meaning, I have seen renewal notices
where no premium had to be paid.
When GST was there, we used to pay only GST.
But now that too has been removed, so you will
not have to pay any premium.
Your policy will be renewed automatically.
Meaning 100% health returns.  100% discount in
a way you get premium pay.  So it
requires being very active.  They have
different segments.  You
have an active lifestyle.  Green, Aber, Red
give you these discounts according to your fitness.  Again you need to download the app.
You get discount only on that basis.
Manipal Cigna also has a
Wealthy app which offers discounts up to 20%.
On the number of steps taken.
Wellness discount up to
30% off is available at Care Supreme.  Discounts are available on consultation,
diagnostic tests, maternity etc.
Pre and post
hospitalization expenses i.e.
expenses incurred before going to the hospital and expenses incurred after that are also
reimbursed.  NIVAPA 3.0 covers 60 days
pre and 180 days post hospitalization
expenses reimbursements.  HDFC Arbo
also offers 60 days free and 180 days post.
90 Days Pre and 180 Days Post in ICIC LB.
Aditya Birla Active One has 90 and
180.  Manipal Singhana Saravaha is 90
& 180 in Param and 60 & 180 in Care Supreme
Plan.  Meaning, here you see that the
pre and post exams should be related to the same thing
due to which you have been
admitted.  For the same hospitalization,
only pre and post treatment is
covered.  E Consultation E
Consultation Unlimited e
consultation is available in Neev Bhupa which you can avail from ivpa health app.
You can e-consult for 51 listed critical illnesses at HDFC Ergo.
You can add unlimited e-consultations in ICIC LBA.
Truth is not covered in Birla.  Then
you will get unlimited e-consultation.
You can get this consultation from Care Supreme Policy in Manipal Singhana Sarawaha Param and through General Physician.  Modern
Treatments and Robotic Surgeries.  So, the
modern treatments that you will see nowadays are that there are
big machines installed in hospitals
which provide treatment in a modern way.
Where traditional surgeries are also
performed in a modern way.  So there are modern
treatments, robotic assisted surgeries.
All those surgeries
are covered in these six policies of yours.  Up to some insure there is
no capping, there is no supplement.
Whatever actual expenses are incurred will be paid.
Non-payable items are an important part.
What are non-payable items?  Like
PPE kits, masks, gloves, all these are
not covered in your policy.  By
default.  Many policies do not cover it.
Most of the policies do not have them.
So you can add these.  If you do not do this,
you may have to pay 10 to 15% at the time of claim.  If it is
not added then the advice is to add it
if it is not inbuilt in your policy.
In Niva Up Resuror 3.0
you can add Claim Safe Card Plus so that all the
non payable items are covered
and your policy becomes fully covered.
HDFC Ago already has the Protect benefit
that can cover you.  ICIC LBA Elevate
also has a Claim Protector Rider which you will have to
add. Aditya Birla Active &
Max has it inbuilt.  There are 147 items that
are covered for you.  In Manipal Sidna Sarvaha Param
plan, you can add NME DMA rider, non-
medical expenses rider, durable
medical expenses rider
and here also in Care Supreme there is claim
shield rider which you can add,
OPD cover is optional in OPD policies,
you can see that, if you want to add it then there is
Well Consult Plus in Niva Reshore 3.0,
you can add it, we have also made a separate video, if
you want to see what are the benefits of OPD,
you can refer to that too,
we will put the link of the video below, HDFC
Ergo Optima Secure has Optima Well
Being Rider which you can add.  ICC Low
Additive has a BeFit rider that you
can add.  OPD is not available at Aditya Birla Eco Activ Max
right now.  Manipal Cigna
also does not have OPD in Param.
You can enter Care in Care OPD Care Supreme.
Copayment.  So copayment is basically
how much you will pay in the claim as a
policy holder.  You are sharing a claim that is
called copayment.  So there is a voluntary comment
in Niva Bupa.  You want to choose.
Right now your 100% claim is payable inbuilt.   If
you want to reduce your premium, then
I want to take co-payment for that, then if I take
20% payment, then
whatever claim comes, you will have to pay 20%, if you
take ventory comment then your
premium gets reduced, so the option
of ventory comment is available, there is
no such option in HDFC Aego Optima Secure,
you can also add rider in your ICICI LBAD Elevate, co-
payment is
not available in Aditya Birla Activ, it
is available in Manipal Cigna, option to choose 10%, 20% and
30%, you can choose co-payment,
this co-payment option is not available in Care.
One of the deductible options is copayment, where
a percentage will be shared in every claim.
Deductible is
an initial amount that will be paid by the
policy holder in every claim.  Lets you take a deductible of ₹10,000 or
₹25,000.  If you get this
claim, you will pay ₹2,000 first once a year.
After that the insurance companies will
pay the claim.  So what will happen with that?  Your
premium will be reduced.  Your
premium which you are paying from LETS is ₹15,000, you will
pay 15,000 or whatever percentage your
deductible and discount on premium will be,
you will pay less premium because
you are saying that you can pay the initial amount.
So
we have made a very good detailed video on deductible where
we have shown the calculation in Excel that
you should take the policy with deductible or
without deductible, you can refer to that also.
We will put the link below.  So
deductible option is available.  Available up to Rs 5 lakh.
In 3.0.  Available up to Rs 5 lakh.
In HDFCO Optima Secure.  Deductible
option is not available in Elevate and Aditya Birla ICICI
Elevate and Aditya Birla Activ Max.
Manipal is also available in Signa Param.
Deductible option is not available in Sarva Param even in Kr.
Premium at slab, so let us see how the premium increases
in the policy.
Lock the clock is available in Neema BPA 3.0.  What lock the
clock means is that
your premium will not increase until you make a claim.
But the premium age slab is five
years.  Someone has taken a policy from Lets for 31 years
and until he makes a claim,
his premium will remain for 31 years.   If you take the
claim, there are slabs of five years
which will increase the premium.  Then comes
HDFC or Go Optima Secure.  There the
premium increases every year with both age and
inflation.  Inflation can impact
your premium at any time.  But the age impact of
HDFC will increase every year.  Then ICICI
LBA Elevate premium increases on 5 year slab.
Inflation can increase at any time,
even in the middle. Then Aditya Bill Active & Max
Five Years Manipal Singhna Sarva 5 Years
and Care Supreme also extend in 5 years.   Let's
talk about waiting periods.  So, the
initial waiting period in all the policies
is 30 days except Manipal Singhna Param
plan where there is no waiting period.
Pre-existing disease waiting period means
if someone already has a disease then what is its
waiting period?  There are three years in Neemaapa.  There
is an option to reduce it to two or one
year or if it comes under 145 illnesses then
you can also bring it to 30 days.
HDFC Ergo has three years.  But if you
take ABCD, Asthma, BP, Cholesterol Diabetes then these
conditions of yours come within 30 days.  ICICI
Elevate also has three years.  But if you
take Jump Start then the waiting period for pre-existing diseases like ABCD,
Asthma, BP, Cholesterol, Diabetes gets
reduced
to 30 days.  Then Aditya will be
active and maximum three years.
Taking chronic care brings your A B CD to Day One.
Waiting period
is not applicable here.  Not Applicable in Manipal Singhana
Sarva.  Care Supreme has a
waiting period of 36 months.  Specific Illnesses
Waiting Period refers to a list of slow-growing illnesses.
That list is in front of you.
This is a standard list which
applies to most of the companies.  Where there are
some things which are
not covered in your policy for two years.  Surgeries like stone,
cataract, hernia, piles, fibroids,
knee replacement, gynecological issues, ENT
issues etc. will
not be covered for your internal continental issues for 24 months.   This
means that if you take a policy today and after a year you
need something, the company will not
give you the claim.  KVPA has a
waiting period of 2 years.  You can reduce it by
paying additional premium.  HDFCO Optima
Secure also has 2 years.  ICIC is
2 years into NBA Deliveroo.  There
is an option to reduce again. Aditya Bill Active &
Max 2 Years 24 Months.  There is
no waiting period in Manipal.  Like there
is a zero waiting period policy.
Also 24 months in Care Supreme.  Then maternity expenses.
So maternity is not covered in Nima 3.0.
You can take a parenthood rider in HDFC Ergo Optima Secure to cover the maternity.
Similarly, you
can also avail maternity and newborn baby coverage under ICIC LMA plan.  To
cover maternity and newborn baby.  Aditya
Birla Active & Max does not offer maternity.
You can add Manipal Signa Param.
Maternity and New Born Baby
Hospitalization through Rider.
Maternity is not covered even in Care Supreme.  Now let's talk about
which riders are available in these
policies. We will talk about them quickly because
detailed videos of these plans are also available on our channel
and we have already talked about these riders
in detail.  Neevapar 3.0 has Cashback
Plus which gives cashback and Neevapar One which
provides you with dedicated services.  You can avail Kasia
Services Elder One for Elder People Annual
Health Checkup.  Heads up is
where you get a discount.  If you
take hospital suggestions for claims from the Niva Bupa team, there is a tiered
network where your network becomes smaller.
The cashless network hospital
list becomes shorter and there are fewer
hospitals but you get 15%
discount.  There is a detailed video
available on tiered network as well.  Please do check that out.
If you are going to choose tier network
then the link is in the
description box.  After that comes
PED Wait Period Modification which is the
wait period of pre-existing disease, Specific
Illness Wait Period Modification Copayment,
Venturi Copayment, Annual Aggregate Deductible,
Personal Accident Cover which covers accidental death
and permanent disability,
Hospital Cash Benefit which is a daily cash benefit for the number of
days you are hospitalized.
Claim Safeguard Plus for non-payable
items Well Consult Plus for OPD
Borderless and Borderless for specified
illnesses.  If we talk about HDFC Ergo, there is
unlimited restore benefit.   There
is hospital cash benefit, critical illness
, IPA, paternity, Optima Well
Being, you can take infinite cover in
which your sum insured becomes infinite.  Then
if we look at the riders of ICICI LAD then
Durable Medical Equipment
Dependent Accommodation Benefit Annual Health
Checkup Claim Protector Power Booster
Infinite Care Air Ambulance Cover
Domestic Network Advantage which is a tiered
network Nursing at Home Compassionate Visit
Inflation Protector which increases your sum assured
every year with inflation
Conviction Benefit Critical Illness Cover Lums
and pays out if a critical illness is
diagnosed Personal Accidental
Benefit which is Accidental Death and Disability
Jump Start to cover your BP Diabetes
from Day One Room Modifier Copayment
Voluntary and Be Fit which is an OPD Rider.
Similarly, Chronic
Care Rider is available in your Aditya Birla and Reducing Room
Category Air Ambulance, all these riders
are available.  You can take a rider to add a waiting period to the Manipal Singh Sarwah Param Plan,
which will
reduce the premium.  Surplus Benefit where
you will get additional 100% of the sum assured from the
first claim of each policy year.  So
from the first year your cover will become 2x.  Personal
accidental cover is available up to Rs 3 crore.
You can add cover for non-medical expenses and durable medical expenses.  Air
Ambulance, Room Rent Modification, Vantary
Copayment, Deductible and Infinite where there
is Infinite cover for listed illnesses.
Your NCB is super in Care Supreme.
100% every year maximum 500% AD weight
period modification available.  Annual
health checkup is available.  Instant cover
is available for hypertension, diabetes,
hyper lipidemia also
known as cholesterol and asthma and
claim shield where your non-payable
items are covered and care OPD rider.
Now let's talk about the premiums and
how much these policies actually cost.
Here we will take a sum assured which will be
same for everyone and show
you the premium with a family size illustration.  There are
no riders included in this.  You can add add-ons as per
your requirement.  So here
we have taken the family size of two adults plus
one child whose age is 35, 32 and four and 10
lakhs and have taken the policy of zone one.
You pay the premium according to your zone.
Whichever city you live in.
Your coverage remains pan India.  So I am sharing the premium
of both ALT and Black in Reshore 3.0 on Niva.
Elite is
2565.
Black's is 29584.   There is
no sum insured here because
unlimited sum is insured.  HDFCO Optima
Secure has a premium of ₹700 for 10 lakhs.  The
ICIC Lambdar Elevate has a
premium of ₹14.94.  Aitya Bla Activ Max carries a
premium of ₹18,584.  And Manipal Signa Sarvaha Ultimate has a
premium of ₹3,758 and K Supreme has a premium of
₹17581.
So now you
can customize the plans as per your choice and
view the riders you want to take.  I
would like to give a disclaimer again that you must do your due diligence
before buying any health insurance policy and if you want to connect with our team then the
number is given.   You
can also take the policy through us.  The number
is given.  You can fill the form.
You can contact us through email ID.  If you have
any feedback,
please tell me in the comment section on what to make the next video.
Quick reminder before we go, if
you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, do so.
So that you get the right infection at
the right time.  See you in the next video.  Till then
stay safe, take care.